sup everyone tizzy Saffy with a very
special for you today now this is gonna
be a lucky unique video clip in my other
views and because like you know
what like I could I could um playing a
game of Overwatch like I was
amazing and like I'm pissed
cuz you know I play a walking and
and I got old man all gold medals I
ain't kidding you
I got gold medals rocket hacking and I
killing I mean your gold man is like
pooping and like I don't give a
and you know what happened is I got
like a mess now I'm not one but
two I guess they're like two friends or
some like like there's a hey like
like they they knew our famous and
like this is why I don't this is what I
hate this is why I hate
that I'm YouTube famous like like it's
good and because I can use my my
fat fat thing I can I can use my I can
use my set you see that this this I mean
I I like I like that Canuck use mark I'm
my faman my famous our city to like like
bring back soccer and you're like how
great sock Underground is although like
in the moments like this people when
they find I'm famous they go on the
attack
they think oh this guy's famous like I
can try to put him down like like he
must be like city's famous he's like
rich he loved soccer on and and you
know what maybe that's true and you know
you I got my money on more
famous I like something on you don't you
know why because I love soccer I know
what's up anyways these two guys I was
playing he'll do you know how I said I
got gold medals I'm saying healing and
and I got all gold medals so they
like if I could like send me a message
saying look you heal excuse me are you
trying to pick a fight with me me I'm
the only five like lucky shot like
I got all the medals who do you know
I was healing at but I was doing
more than you and anyways so I child
like I told you news to people right I
said I told one of them get out of
my face do not send me a message
and he like got scared and like
never run again but the other got
neither he don't know what to do when
you messed hated by a
he continued messaging me even after I'm
home I'm the five I could I could
tell when I told that his message like
slow down cuz like his pants or
some and I like yeah that's right
so you know I did I challenged him to a
1v1 and I kicked his ass you
don't mess with me you just don't
do that
like like I don't know what his deal was
like I personal thing
i personal think that he was like
jealous and like what the
get good I play I
watch Sonic Underground ID I got more
hate from modern Sonic fans and I deal
with that more than you can handle
like when you get explosive diarrhea
after eating Taco Bell you know I'm you
picking up what I'm putting down
yeah this is why I hate being
famous P think think
that oh because he's famous like people
think that just because he's famous they
think like he's good and yes I am
what the I watch Sonic
Underground you know the ship oh darling
look I told him that I said she
know about our new kids and he said oh
yeah I heard about that
that's like Sonic X bar would be like
like he that's he said he said it before
that is my favorite
Oh your team was only four five and I
said yes I
are you kidding me like it fit it
together all the final did he see how
good I wasn't on watch you you cannot be
that gonna know watch unless you're me
unless you're me you know this
everybody knows this that's
what's up
I like I ain't kiddin around big a
facade on a no fan I deal with hatred
anger and ugliness for Mars our fans
every day do you really think that you
can be me do you think you think you can
put me down
that's funny ha ha
I'm tired of this I don't
even know what the I'm making this
video I can't tell you what though I'd
sooner make this video I am gonna send
it to him I'm gonna send it to his mama
I'm gonna said to his daddy I'm gonna
I'm gonna fight with his kids go to
school that I'm gonna go to school I'm
gonna first of all punch his kids in the
face then give him like I didn't show
those kids like I this
video then they'll cry and think
daddy doesn't like Sonic on the ground
or a team with me five cuz you know like
I got tenders ourselves you know
damn well that you're chill knows who
the I am like they don't like
veal beat your ass for me they'll be
your ass for me you can you understand
come on pooper baby
you're funny
no you're not funny you're weak you're
weak
that's what